gamecpm.com 2016-11-24

# GameCPM - Game Advertising Network

**Privacy Policy**

GameCPM remains committed to ensure complete confidentiality of personal information of their clients and therefore follow a strict privacy policy for their customers. Privacy policy at GameCPM ensures to preserve the peace of the virtual environment and keep the identity of the customer completely safe and secure from prying eyes.

GameCPM understands the importance of your privacy and therefore safeguarding your personal information is of the utmost importance. Browse through the following 

Privacy Policy and procedures concerning the collection and use of any website material. A version of this Privacy Policy will be posted if you are on one of our websites. We correspond to online publishers and their properties to advertisers and sustain other properties supported by advertiser clients. Safeguarding your personal information is of the utmost importance as we realize the importance of your privacy.

This Privacy Policy at GameCPM will be revised from time to time. You will be notified of any such changes and whenever a new policy regarding the privacy is posted. Visit the site regularly regarding any such new policy and verify any changes to this Privacy Policy. You can always contact the customer care if you have any questions regarding our privacy practices.  
**  
Registration**

When registering at GameCPM, the information collected will include your name, username, phone number, email address, company name and address, date of birth, account password etc. Your IP address will also get collected at the time of your registration and while using the site. In order to become the advertiser for GameCPM, one will need to register and you may require additional services and features as well as promotional opportunities. You may need to submit additional information to participate.

**Information Collected**

We collect information regarding our Sites and Services when registering for an account and contribution in surveys, contests, sweepstakes and promotions, contacting GameCPM and visit and browsing any our sites.

**Use of cookies**

Cookies store information that is placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most Web browsers accept cookies characteristically but one can always change your browser settings to check this. Any information or features of our website can be used even without a cookie. Any personal information of users at GameCPM is used only for maintaining the website.

**Surveys and Promotions**

Any information related to your web browsing sessions is also collected while participating in any Surveys and Promotions. GameCPM coordinates the marketing support that allows publishers to carry on allocating their knowledge, views and insights. However, it is optional to partake in Surveys and Promotions. The information included for the Surveys and Promotions may consist of your name, address, phone number, -mail address and website.

**Anonymous Information**

Anonymous Information too is collected at GameCPM such as general usage patterns, traffic statistics, regarding dates, page views, dates and times you make use of the Site. Information regarding files accessed through the Site, how you were referred to the website, responses sent to the browser, and the data sent to the browser is also available. Records are kept for any other communication between browser and Sites. GameCPM does not make use of cookies for any other activities on any of our websites.

The Anonymous Information is solely used for the purpose of system administration, targeted advertising, offering certain site content and functionality, collecting and reporting aggregate usage and for site tracking. Your Personally Identifiable Information and Anonymous Information may be used in combination to inform you of any special offers and target advertising. 

**Contacting GameCPM**  
GameCPM may be contacted by submitting a form through a Site, or by giving a feedback. When you contact GameCPM through a Site, your name and complete email address will get conveyed to the website and stored on our web servers.

**How Information is collected and used**

GameCPM remains completely committed to ensure your complete privacy and security while visiting the website anytime. Advanced 128-bit encryption technology is used to make sure that our web pages are secure from any unauthorized access. 

Any information that is used to locate and identify you is your Personally Identifiable Information. This information is used solely to correspond with you regarding such Services as well as offer information that you have requested on our products and services such as e-mail newsletters, membership updates, advertising insertion as well as to collect fees, resolve any disputes and troubleshoot problems. Personally Identifiable Information may also be used to answer to any specific inquiries made by you and prevent any illegal activities. The main objective is to improve our Services as well as customize and measure the content, and layout. 

Your Personally Identifiable Information is also used and analyzed to notify you regarding any of our special services, offers, products, and supplement it with other information that would be of use to you and may interest you. The purpose is to 

gauge the effectiveness of advertisements on our Sites and Publisher Properties.

**Sharing Information**

You Personal Information WILL NOT be shared with third parties, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Your privacy is of utmost important to us and before we collect any personal information, the user will get the exact reasons for which information is being collected at GameCPM.

**Phishing**

Your credit card information, login password, username, national identification numbers WILL NOT at any time be requested for at GameCPM, in telephone communication or an unsolicited e-mail. Identity theft, also referred to as phishing are of great concern to GameCPM and every step is taken to help protect you from identity theft.

**Posting**

Any information that is posted and voluntarily disclosed by our users on our site, for example in web logs, message boards, chat areas etc. may be used and viewed by others. Any personal information posted at GameCPM by the user holds him or her responsible and they are doing so at their own risk. One may receive uncalled-for messages from other parties in return.

**Third Party Service Providers**

Only a few and certain trusted third parties are engaged at GameCPM to provide services and carry out various functions, such as maintenance services and web hosting services. These 3rd parties may perhaps have admittance to some of your Personally Identifiable Information, but only to perform necessary functions and improve the services.

**Modifying** **Your Information**

One may access and alter their Personally Identifiable Information any time with the help of the "sign in" area at the GameCPM Domain. You may not be able to amend the Personally Identifiable Information through other parts of the GameCPM Domain or other Sites. One can contact the customer care if this is of any concern to them.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

Some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information may be disclosed to the law enforcement officials, government or private parties, as, at GameCPM, we believe that it important and right to abide by the law and comply with legal process. It is important for us to protect the rights of GameCPM and third party and ensure the safety of the public or any person. It is essential to prevent any unethical or illegal activity as well as respond to legal complaints.

**Security and safety**

Certain technological, physical and procedural measures are taken at GameCPM for the complete safety and security of your Personally Identifiable Information and keep it safe from any unauthorized use and access. Servers containing Personally Identifiable Information are stores in an off-site facility. Advanced 128-bit encryption technology, along with the use of hashed passwords and using algorithmic version of your password is stored so as to keep your actual password concealed.

Secure Sockets Layer or SSL are used when getting financial information in connection for completing certain online transactions. However, the users should keep in mind that no matter how secure or safe industry standard security protocol is, there is always a possibility that a security breach could occur.

**Associations with other sites**

Each GameCPM Site may consist of linking to other websites. Therefore, as a user, it is your responsibility to see which website one is visiting when presenting any personally identifiable information. The Privacy Policy at GameCPM deals with the use and disclosure of only that information that is collected through different Sites with us. However, there may be different rules applying to information submitted to other websites including their Publisher Properties. Always review the privacy policies of these websites before submitting any information.

**Our Policy for Children**

Any individual, less than eighteen years of age is not permitted to offer his personally identifiable information at GameCPM. Any parent who becomes aware that his or her child has offered any sensitive information at our website, needs to contact our customer care. If the authorities at GameCPM become aware that that a child under 19 has offered any personally identifiable information, then any such information is removed.

**Changes in commercial ownership**

Any changes in the assets of GameCPM or any merges with another entity would mean that your Personally Identifiable Information would be shared with that entity. Any personal information is collected by lawful and fair means and with the rightful consent of the individual concerned.
